<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE plist PUBLIC "-//Apple//DTD PLIST 1.0//EN" "http://www.apple.com/DTDs/PropertyList-1.0.dtd">
<plist version="1.0">
    <array>
		<array>
			<string>Intro to Basic Concepts (micro)</string>
			<array>
				<string>a19</string>
				<string>A certain economy can only produce corn and computers. The graph that shows how many computers they can produce for their choosen level of corn production is called:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a165</string>
				<string>What is the main contraint in the allocation of resources?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>2</string>
				<string>If country a can produce 2 mango or 4 bananas, what is the opportunity cost (in bananas) to produce 1 mango?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a180</string>
				<string>When Bryan goes to a concert, he gives up $100 in wages, $19 dollars for a ticket, and another $19 to bring Joshua. These costs are called his:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a184</string>
				<string>When people must decide between two things they are making a:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a65</string>
				<string>Joshua can write 6 multiple choice or 2 open response, while Bryan can write 8 multiple choice or 4 open response. What advantage does Joshua have in writing multiple choice?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a40</string>
				<string>Joshua can write 6 multiple choice or 2 open response, while Bryan can write 8 multiple choice or 4 open response. What advantage does Bryan have in writing multiple choice?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a139</string>
				<string>"The government should provide free healthcare," what type of statement is that?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a140</string>
				<string>"The government doesn't provide free hover-cars," what type of statement is that?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Supply and Demand (micro)</string>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>An improvement in production technology causes what to happen to the price?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>If the amount of buyers increases, what happens to quantity produced?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a39</string>
				<string>If the amount of suppliers in a market increases, what happens to demand?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a67</string>
				<string>Joshua always buys bagels and tubs of cream cheese together, to Joshua bagels and cream cheese are what type of goods?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a68</string>
				<string>Bryan enjoys coffee and orange juice, however he always has one or the other, to Bryan coffee and orange juice are what type of goods?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a114</string>
				<string>Bryan starts winning more economics competitions and makes more money; with that money he buys more suits. To Bryan suits are what type of good?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a114</string>
				<string>Joshua takes a sabbatical in Fiji and his income goes down, because of this he buys less video games. To Joshua video games are what type of good?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a113</string>
				<string>Joshua takes a sabbatical in Fiji and his income goes down, because of this he buys more flip-flops. To Joshua flip-flops are what type of good?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>As the price of peanut butter increases, what happens to the price of jelly, a complementary good?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>As the demand for pens decreases, what happens to the price of paper, a complementary good?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>As Joshua treats hamburgers and hotdogs as substitute goods. What will happen to the quantity of hot dogs he demands when the price of hamburgers increases?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>According to the law of demand, quanity decreases if price does what?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a5</string>
				<string>If the government subsidizes the production of computers, which curve will increase in the computer market</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Elasticity, Price Controls, Taxes, Consumer Surplus (micro)</string>
			<array>
				<string>a17</string>
				<string>Bryan decides that he should increase the price of pizza at his store. He must believe that pizza is: </string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a17</string>
				<string>Bryan increase the price of pizza at his store and starts making less revenue, the pizza is a(n) ___ good</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>Econ Textbooks Inc has an economic consultant come in. If the consultant determiens the books are elastic goods, he will advise the comapny to do what to their price to increase profit?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a214</string>
				<string>A binding price floor is imposed on a good, their is now a ___ of the good.</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a39</string>
				<string>A price ceiling is imposed above the equilibrium price, how is the quanity affected?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a90</string>
				<string>A producer raises their prices by exactly $6.14 and finds that they still sell the exact same amount. The good is considered to be ___.</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>If the producer of an elastic good raises their prices, what will happen to their total revenue?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a16</string>
				<string>If the government says that a certain company may not sell above a certain level, the government has imposed a what?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a67</string>
				<string>If the cross price elasticity of demand is negative, the goods are what type of goods?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>4</string>
				<string>Calculate the coeffeciant of price elasticity if a 4% increase in price causes a 16% increase in quantity demanded.</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Consumer Choice (micro)</string>
			<array>
				<string>0</string>
				<string>Calculate the value of marginal utility when utility is maximized.</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>6</string>
				<string>Joshua loves chips($2) and cookies($3), if his utility is maximized and his last cookie provided him with 4 utils, how many utils did his last cookie provide?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a222</string>
				<string>If Bryan's marginal utility never decreases, what is his demand curve like</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a111</string>
				<string>A (normal) good's price increases and makes the buyers feel poorer causing them to purchase less of it, this effect is called:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a112</string>
				<string>A (normal) good's price increases and makes buyers buy more substitutes, this effect is called:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a80</string>
				<string>Each slice of pizza provides Joshua with less and less satisfaction, this is called:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>1</string>
				<string>Let a be the marginal utility per dollar of good a, and b be the mu/$ of good b. If total utility is maximized, a/b is:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Costs of production (micro)</string>
			<array>
				<string>a100</string>
				<string>In the long run there are no:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a4</string>
				<string>The average cost for producing a product:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>6</string>
				<string>(In dollars, i.e. "3") the marginal cost for the 4 unit is:</string>
				<string>3</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>16</string>
				<string>(In dollars, i.e. "3") ATC for producing 6 units:</string>
				<string>3</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>24</string>
				<string>(In dollars, i.e. "3") Fixed Costs:</string>
				<string>3</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>1</string>
				<string>(In dollars, i.e. "3") Unit afterwhich diminishing marginal returns are experianced:</string>
				<string>3</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>12</string>
				<string>(In dollars, i.e. "3") AFC for producing two units:</string>
				<string>3</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a14</string>
				<string>What must go down as more units are produced:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a39</string>
				<string>What change will an increase in the rent of the factory have on ATC in the short run?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>What change will an increase in the rent of the factory have on ATC in the long run?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a2</string>
				<string>Change in total cost divided by change in quanity equals</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a82</string>
				<string>When Joshua doubles all inputs and output more than doubles he is experiancing:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a83</string>
				<string>When Bryan halves all inputs and output more than halves he is experiancing:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>PC and Monopolies (micro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Oligopolies and Monopolistic Competition (micro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Markets for Factors of Production (micro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Externalities (micro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Intro, GDP, CPI, Unemployment, Inflation (macro)</string>
			<array>
				<string>a122</string>
				<string>What is a term used to describe the buying of 15 new sewing machines by an apparel company?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a34</string>
				<string>What is the name of the situation in which an individual is without a job but is looking for work?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a118</string>
				<string>What type of unemployment is experienced for a worker who is unemployed because his skills are obsolete?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a117</string>
				<string>What type of unemployment is experienced for a recent college graduate who is looking for her first job?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>2000</string>
				<string>Assume that last year's CPI was 150 and nominal income was $30,000. If today's CPI is 160, how much does nominal income need to increase for the same real income?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>5</string>
				<string>If nominal income rises 4% and real income falls 1%, what is the percent change in price level?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a215</string>
				<string>Which of the following best measures the change in price level of national product: consumer price index, GDP deflator, or producer price index?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a171</string>
				<string>What model shows the relationship between the transfer of goods and services between households and industries?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a219</string>
				<string>At what point is this economy producing at an allocatively inefficient level? ("Point _")</string>
				<string>2</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a220</string>
				<string>At what point would this economy be producing at an impossible level?</string>
				<string>2</string>
			</array>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>AD, AS, LRAS, and Econ Growth (macro)</string>
			<array>
				<string>a39</string>
				<string>Which way will the demand curve as a result of an improvement in technology?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>Which way will the supply curve shift as a result of an improvement in technology?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>Improved productivity would ___ real income per capita.</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>An increased population size and not change in productivity would ___ real income per capita.</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>An increase in oil prices would shift SRAS which direction?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a39</string>
				<string>A rightward shift of AD would cause SRAS to shift what direction?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>A decrease in taxes would shift AD what direction?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>A government policy that encourages saving and investment would shift LRAS which direction?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>What will happen to unemployment if consumption spending increases?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a221</string>
				<string>What shape is the AS curve in the long run?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a39</string>
				<string>What would happen to U.S. GDP if an American entrepreneur founds and locates a software company in London?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>In an economy with a horizontal supply curve, an increase in government spending will cause output to change in what way?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Financial Sector: Money, Banking, and the Fed (macro)</string>
			<array>
				<string>a210</string>
				<string>What is the largest component of the M1 money supply?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>40000</string>
				<string>If the reserve requirement is 25% and banks have excess reserves of $10,000, what is the maximum amount of additional money that can be created through the lending process?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Monetary and Fiscal Policy (macro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Phillips curve, loanable funds, and Exchange Rate (macro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Crimson Vocubulary (extra)</string>
		</array>
	</array>
</plist>
