<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE plist PUBLIC "-//Apple//DTD PLIST 1.0//EN" "http://www.apple.com/DTDs/PropertyList-1.0.dtd">
<plist version="1.0">
    <array>
		<array>
			<string>Intro to Basic Concepts (micro)</string>
			<array>
				<string>a19</string>
				<string>A certain economy can only produce corn and computers. The graph that shows how many computers they can produce for their choosen level of corn production is called:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a165</string>
				<string>What is the main contraint in the allocation of resources?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>2</string>
				<string>If country a can produce 2 mango or 4 bananas, what is the opportunity cost (in bananas) to produce 1 mango?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a180</string>
				<string>When Bryan goes to a concert, he gives up $100 in wages, $19 dollars for a ticket, and another $19 to bring Joshua. These costs are called his:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a184</string>
				<string>When people must decide between two things they are making a:</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a65</string>
				<string>Joshua can write 6 multiple choice or 2 open response, while Bryan can write 8 multiple choice or 4 open response. What advantage does Joshua have in writing multiple choice?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a40</string>
				<string>Joshua can write 6 multiple choice or 2 open response, while Bryan can write 8 multiple choice or 4 open response. What advantage does Bryan have in writing multiple choice?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a139</string>
				<string>"The government should provide free healthcare," what type of statement is that?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a140</string>
				<string>"The government doesn't provide free hover-cars," what type of statement is that?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Supply and Demand (micro)</string>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>An improvement in production technology causes what to happen to the price?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>If the amount of buyers increases, what happens to quantity produced?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a39</string>
				<string>If the amount of suppliers in a market increases, what happens to demand?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a67</string>
				<string>Joshua always buys bagels and tubs of cream cheese together, to Joshua bagels and cream cheese are what type of goods?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a68</string>
				<string>Bryan enjoys coffee and orange juice, however he always has one or the other, to Bryan coffee and orange juice are what type of goods?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a114</string>
				<string>Bryan starts winning more economics competitions and makes more money; with that money he buys more suits. To Bryan suits are what type of good?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a114</string>
				<string>Joshua takes a sabbatical in Fiji and his income goes down, because of this he buys less video games. To Joshua video games are what type of good?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a113</string>
				<string>Joshua takes a sabbatical in Fiji and his income goes down, because of this he buys more flip-flops. To Joshua flip-flops are what type of good?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>As the price of peanut butter increases, what happens to the price of jelly, a complementary good?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>As the demand for pens decreases, what happens to the price of paper, a complementary good?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>As Joshua treats hamburgers and hotdogs as substitute goods. What will happen to the quantity of hot dogs he demands when the price of hamburgers increases?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a37</string>
				<string>According to the law of demand, quanity decreases if price does what?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a5</string>
				<string>If the government subsidizes the production of computers, which curve will increase in the computer market</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Elasticity, Price Controls, Taxes, Consumer Surplus (micro)</string>
			<array>
				<string>a17</string>
				<string>Bryan decides that he should increase the price of pizza at his store. He must believe that pizza is: </string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a17</string>
				<string>Bryan increase the price of pizza at his store and starts making less revenue, the pizza is a(n) ___ good</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>Econ Textbooks Inc has an economic consultant come in. If the consultant determiens the books are elastic goods, he will advise the comapny to do what to their price?</string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
			<array>
				<string>a38</string>
				<string>A binding price floor is imposed, their is now a </string>
				<string>0</string>
			</array>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Consumer Choice (micro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Costs of production (micro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>PC and Monopolies (micro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Oligopolies and Monopolistic Competition (micro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Markets for Factors of Production (micro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Intro, GDP, Unemployment, Inflation (macro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>AD, AS, LRAS, and Econ Growth (macro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Financial Sector: Money, Banking, and the Fed (macro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Monetary and Fiscal Policy (macro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Phillips curve, loanable funds, and Exchange Rate (macro)</string>
		</array>
		<array>
			<string>Crimson Vocubulary (extra)</string>
		</array>
	</array>
</plist>
